Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2013
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Yehudi Wyner and Michael Lipsey at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2839 Yehudi Wyber and .tif (Image-file jib2013_084)
- Audience, including Zane Merritt, Daniel Bassin, Megan Grace Beugger, and Clinton Haycraft, at Talujon Percussion Ensemble performance featuring works of June in Buffalo 2013 participants, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2841 4 PM concert featering JIB participants at Slee B1.tif (Image-file jib2013_085)
- Matthew Ward conducting the others members of the Talujon Percussion Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2844 4pm concert.tif (Image-file jib2013_086)
- David Cossin playing a conch shell June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2851John Cage Talujon Percussion Ensemble.tif (Image-file jib2013_087)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble setup of cans for performance at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2854 John Cage .tif (Image-file jib2013_088)
- Percussionist Ian Antonio at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2858 Talujon Percussion Ensemble.tif (Image-file jib2013_089)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2869 Talujon Percussion Ensemble John Cage.tif (Image-file jib2013_090)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Ian Antonio, Matthew Ward, and David Cossin performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2877 Talujon Percussion Ensemble.tif (Image-file jib2013_091)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members David Cossin and Tom Kolor performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2878 Talujon Percussion Ensemble.tif (Image-file jib2013_092)
- JACK Quartet performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2890 Jack Quartet====------.tif (Image-file jib2013_093)
- JACK Quartet and Irvine Arditti at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2892Jack Quartet and Irvin Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2013_094)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Ian Antonio, Tom Kolor, David Cossin, and Matthew Ward performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2902 Talujon Percussion Ensemble.tif (Image-file jib2013_095)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Tom Kolor, Ian Antonio, David Cossin, and Matthew Ward performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2905Talujon Percussion Ensemble.tif (Image-file jib2013_096)
- Composer John Chittum and conductor Brad Lubman with members of SIGNAL Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2911 John Chittam JIB participants with SIGNAL.tif (Image-file jib2013_097)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and composer Brien Henderson at SIGNAL Ensemble rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2917SIGNAL rehearsal with Brien Henderson.tif (Image-file jib2013_098)
- Daniel Bassin and Colin Tucker with conductor Jean-Philippe Wurtz at rehearsal with Ensemble Linea at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2920.tif (Image-file jib2013_099)
- Daniel Bassin and Colin Tucker with conductor Jean-Philippe Wurtz at rehearsal with Ensemble Linea at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Colin Tucker Daniel Bassin with Linea Ensemble.tif (Image-file jib2013_100)
- Ensemble Linea members Jessica Rona, Maiko Matsuoka, and Johannes Burghoff rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2921LINEA rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2013_101)
- Conductor Jean-Philippe Wurtz talking with composer Brian Herrington at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2922LINEA rehearsal with Brian Herrington.tif (Image-file jib2013_102)
- Composer Eric Stewart at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2926rehearsal Eric Stewart.tif (Image-file jib2013_103)
- Composer Valentina Velkovska with violinist Maiko Matsuoka at a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2931Valentina Velkovska rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2013_104)
- Colin Tucker, Jacob Gotlib, Brian Ferneyhough, Zane Merritt, Jenny Beck, and Jonghee Kang in composition master class at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2937Brian Ferneyhough Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_105)
- Yehudi Wyner teaching master class at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2951Yehudi Wyner Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_106)
- Student composers James Young, Tomas Gueglio, Steven Weimer, and Esin Gündüz in Raphael Cendo's master class at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2957Raphael Cendo CLASS.tif (Image-file jib2013_107)
- Raphael Cendo teaching a master class at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2962Raphael Cendo CLASS.tif (Image-file jib2013_108)
- Ethan Herschenfeld, Steven Brennfleck, Laura Mercado Wright, and Sharon Harms rehearsing Charles Wuorinen's It happens like this at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2966singers in Wuorinen concert.tif (Image-file jib2013_109)
- Charles Wuorinen conducting members of the Slee Sinfonietta and singers Ethan Herschenfeld, Steven Brennfleck, Laura Mercado Wright, and Sharon Harms in rehearsal of his It happens like this at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2967Wuorinen rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2013_110)
- Ethan Herschenfeld rehearsing Charles Wuorinen's It happens like this at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2968 Ethan Herschenfeld.tif (Image-file jib2013_111)
- Charles Wuorinen conducting the Slee Sinfonietta in a rehearsal of his It Happens like this at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2969 It Happens Like That rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2013_112)
- Charles Wuorinen conducting the Slee Sinfonietta and singers Ethan Herschenfeld, Steven Brennfleck, Laura Mercado Wright, and Sharon Harms in a rehearsal of his It happens like this at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2975Wuorinen concert rehearsal It Happens Like That.tif (Image-file jib2013_113)
- Composer Jason Thorpe Buchanan demonstrating a bowing to members of Ensemble Linea and its conductor Jean-Philippe Wurtz at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Jason Thorpe Buchanan-.tif (Image-file jib2013_114)
- Composer Jason Thorpe Buchanan rehearsing with Ensemble Linea violist Jessica Rona at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_2997Jason Thorpe Buchanan rehearsing.tif (Image-file jib2013_115)
- Ensemble Linea violoncellist Johannes Burghoff rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3001rehearsing.tif (Image-file jib2013_116)
- Composer Jason Thorpe Buchanan demonstrating a string technique on the violin while rehearsing with the Ensemble Linea at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3005Brian Thorpe Buchanan.tif (Image-file jib2013_117)
- Composer Esin Gunduz rehearses her States of Iron with clarinetist Andrea Nagy and flutist Keiko Murakami of the Ensemble Linea at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3009Esin Guenduez States of Iron rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2013_118)
- Concert manager Philip Rehard at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Philip Rehard concert manager.tif (Image-file jib2013_119)
- Charles Wuorinen receives a SUNY honorary doctorate from University at Buffalo President Satish K. Tripathi and SUNY Trustee Eunice Lewin, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3097 Dr. Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_120)
- Charles Wuorinen receives a SUNY honorary doctorate from University at Buffalo President Satish K. Tripathi and SUNY Trustee Eunice Lewin, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3101 Dr. Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_121)
- President Satish K. Tripathi presents Charles Wuorinen with a SUNY honorary doctorate with composer David Felder and SUNY Trustee Eunice Lewin applauding, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3106=Dr. Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_122)
- Charles Wuorinen speaks at the ceremony at which he was awarded a SUNY honorary doctorate, with composer David Felder, University President Satish K. Tripathi, and SUNY Trustee Eunice Lewin on stage, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3110Dr. Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_123)
- David Felder at the podium at the ceremony awarding Charles Wuorinen a SUNY honorary doctorate, with University President Satish K. Tripathi, and SUNY Trustee Eunice Lewin, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3112--Dr. Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_124)
- David Felder speaks at the ceremony awarding Charles Wuorinen a SUNY honorary doctorate, with University President Satish K. Tripathi, and SUNY Trustee Eunice Lewin, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Dr.David Felder Charles Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_125)
- JACK Quartet and Eric Huebner performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: IMG_0019 Jack Quartet.tif (Image-file jib2013_126)
- Charles Wuorinen conducting the Slee Sinfonietta and singers Ethan Herschenfeld, Steven Brennfleck, Laura Mercado Wright, and Sharon Harms in a performance of his It happens like this at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: IT Happens Like That Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_127)
- James Baker conducting the Talea Ensemble at a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3137rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2013_128)
- JACK Quartet with student composer Jeffrey Holmes at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3143Jack Quartet with Jeffrey Holmes student composer.tif (Image-file jib2013_129)
- JACK Quartet with student composer Andrew Greenwald at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3146Jack Quartet with student composer.tif (Image-file jib2013_130)
- Student composers Jonghee Kang and Jeffrey Holmes at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Jonghee Kang Jeffrey Holmes.tif (Image-file jib2013_131)
- Charles Wuorinen and the Slee Sinfonietta after the performance of It Happens Like This at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: It Happens like That Wuorinen.tif (Image-file jib2013_132)
- Violist Elizabeth Weisser at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3172 viola.tif (Image-file jib2013_133)
- James Baker conducting the Talea Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3194James Baker conductor.tif (Image-file jib2013_134)
- Clarinetist Rane Moore performing a piece by Raphael Cendo at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3196 Cendo.tif (Image-file jib2013_135)
- Composer Raphael Cendo and clarinetist Rane Moore at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3205after concert.tif (Image-file jib2013_136)
- Yehudi Wyner with pianist Steven Beck at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3209Yehudi Wyner St Beck.tif (Image-file jib2013_137)
- David Felder with members of Talea Ensemble after a performance of Requiescat at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Dr.David Felder.tif (Image-file jib2013_138)
- Brian Ferneyhough shaking hands with violist Elizabeth Weisser after the performance of Incipits at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3214end of concert.tif (Image-file jib2013_139)
- Conductor James Baker applauding composer Brian Ferneyhough and violist Elizabeth Weisser at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3220Brian Ferneyhough.tif (Image-file jib2013_140)
- Irvine Arditti playing violin at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3234Irvin Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2013_141)
- Composer Kurt Isaacson talking with double bassist Doug Balliett at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3253rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2013_142)
- Conductor James Baker talking with composer Stylianos Dimou at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Stylianos Dimou.tif (Image-file jib2013_143)
- Conductor James Baker talking with composer Eric Stewart at rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3258rehearsal with Talea Ensemble.tif (Image-file jib2013_144)
- Brian Ferneyhough at a lecture at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3269Brian Ferneyhough lecture.tif (Image-file jib2013_145)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove and composer Jonghee Kang at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3291Jonathan Golove Jonghee Kang.tif (Image-file jib2013_146)
- Augusta Read Thomas talking to student composers during her class at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3312Augusta Read Thomas Class.tif (Image-file jib2013_147)
- Sound engineer Chris Jacobs at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3320 Chris Jacobs Audio Technical Director.tif (Image-file jib2013_148)
- Sound engineer Chris Jacobs at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Chris Jacobs Audio Technical Director.tif (Image-file jib2013_149)
- James Baker conducting the Talea Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3334James Baker conducting.tif (Image-file jib2013_150)
- James Baker conducting the Talea Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3336James Baker conducting.tif (Image-file jib2013_151)
- James Baker conducting the Talea Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3339----Talea Ensemble Thursday.tif (Image-file jib2013_152)
- James Baker conducting the Talea Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3342James Baker conducting.tif (Image-file jib2013_153)
- James Baker conducting the Talea Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Talea Ensemble Stylianos Dimou UNTITLED.jpg (Image-file jib2013_154)
- Pianist Anna D'Errico at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3356Anne d Errico.tif (Image-file jib2013_155)
- Pianist Anna D'Errico at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3358Anne d Eririco.tif (Image-file jib2013_156)
- Pianist Anna D'Errico at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3364Anne d Errico.tif (Image-file jib2013_157)
- Jean-Philippe Wurtz conducting Ensemble Linea at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3370Ensemble Linea June 6 2013 .tif (Image-file jib2013_158)
- Conductor Jean-Philippe Wurtz and members of Ensemble Linea taking a bow after performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3372 Ensemble Linea.tif (Image-file jib2013_159)
- Violist Jessica Rona and clarinetist Andrea Nagy performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3374 Andrea Nagy clarinet Jessica Rona viola in RASH by.tif (Image-file jib2013_160)
- Jean-Philippe Wurtz conducting Ensemble Linea at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3375Ensemble Linea June 6 3013.tif (Image-file jib2013_161)
- Keiko Murakami playing the bass flute at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3378Keiko Murakami flute Ensemble Linea-.tif (Image-file jib2013_162)
- Jean-Philippe Wurtz conducting members of Ensemble Linea performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3379Ensemble Linea.tif (Image-file jib2013_163)
- Maiko Matsuoka playing violin at June in buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3385Maiko Matsuoka Ensemble Linea.tif (Image-file jib2013_164)
- Johannes Burghoff playing violoncello at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3391Johannes Burghoff Cello Ensewmble Linea.tif (Image-file jib2013_165)
- Raphael Cendo with violist Jessica Rona and clarinetist Andrea Nagy after a performance of Rokh I at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3402composer Raphael Cendo Ensemble Linea June 6.tif (Image-file jib2013_166)
- Melanie Aceto performing Megan Grace Beugger's piece, Liaison at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3438Melanie Aceto.jpg (Image-file jib2013_167)
- Melanie Aceto performing Megan Grace Beugger's piece, Liaison at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Melanie Aceto in Megan Breugger tiff.tif (Image-file jib2013_168)
- Melanie Aceto performing Megan Grace Beugger's piece, Liaison at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3452Megan Breugger Melanie Aceto.tif (Image-file jib2013_169)
- Melanie Aceto performing Megan Grace Beugger's piece, Liaison at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3466Melanie Aceto--.tif (Image-file jib2013_170)
- Melanie Aceto performing Megan Grace Beugger's piece, Liaison at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3471Melanie Aceto.tif (Image-file jib2013_171)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas and saxophonist Ken Radnofsky in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3501Read Thomas and Ken Radnofsky.tif (Image-file jib2013_172)
- Saxophonist Ken Radnofsky, conductor Brad Lubman, and composer Augusta Read Thomas in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3508Brad Lubman with Augusta Read Thomas.tif (Image-file jib2013_173)
- Jean-Philippe Wurtz conducting members of Ensemble Linea in performance of Asymptotic Flux: First Study in Entrophy by Jason Thorpe Buchanan at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3510Ensemble Linea.tif (Image-file jib2013_174)
- Jean-Philippe Wurtz conducting members of Ensemble Linea in performance of Asymptotic Flux: First Study in Entrophy by Jason Thorpe Buchanan at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: student composer Jason Thorpe Buchaban piece performed by 0E.tif (Image-file jib2013_175)
- Conductor Jean-Philippe Wurtz and members of Ensemble Linea applauding student composer Jason Thorpe Buchanan after the performance of his Asymptotic flux at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3511Ensemble Linea and student composer.tif (Image-file jib2013_176)
- Conductor Jean-Philippe Wurtz and members of Ensemble Linea applauding student composer Jason Thorpe Buchanan after the performance of his Asymptotic flux at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: student composer Jason Thorpe Buchanan with Ensemble Linea.tif (Image-file jib2013_177)
- Composer Esin Gunduz performing her work States of Iron with Ensemble Linea members Keiko Murakami and Andrea Nagy at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3513Esin Guenduez STATES OF IRON.tif (Image-file jib2013_178)
- Composer Esin Gunduz performing her work States of Iron with Ensemble Linea members Keiko Murakami and Andrea Nagy at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Esin Guenduez STATES OF IRON.tif (Image-file jib2013_179)
- Violoncellist T. J. Borden performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3525JT Bordem.tif (Image-file jib2013_180)
- Violoncellist T. J. Borden performing at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3531JT Borden.tif (Image-file jib2013_181)
- View of score over shoulder of violoncellist T. J. Borden at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3536score.tif (Image-file jib2013_182)
- Violoncellist T. J. Borden, percussionist Ross Aftel, and pianist Nicholas Emmanuel performing at the Performance Institute Program at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3537Baird Recital Hall.tif (Image-file jib2013_183)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti performs at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3540RDITTI--.tif (Image-file jib2013_184)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove with student composers Jonghee Kang, and Ursula Kwong-Brown at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3542 Jonathan Golove Jonghee Kang Ursukla Kwong-Brown.tif (Image-file jib2013_185)